USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 1: Photographic Materials, 1915-1962
  - Subseries 2: USS Arizona and Personnel Photographs, 1916-1941
    - USS Arizona Crew Firing Anti-Aircraft Guns at a Target in the Air, 84-26-17, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Trophies Displayed on USS Arizona deck, 84-26-18, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-19, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-20, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Full Crew on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-21, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Navy Admirals on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-22, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Number 4 Turret Crew of USS Arizona on Deck, 84-26-23, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - USS Arizona Band Playing on Deck, 84-26-24, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - USS Arizona Band on Deck, 84-26-25, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Navy Admirals with Unidentified Sailors Standing at Attention on USS Arizona Deck, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Navy Admiral Inspecting 3rd Division on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-27, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Navy Admiral Inspecting Marine Guard on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-28, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Navy Admiral Inspecting Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-29, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Navy Admiral Inspecting Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-30, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Navy Admiral Inspecting Sea Bags of the Boilers Division on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-31, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Navy Admiral Inspecting the Repair Division on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-32, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Navy Captain Inspecting Sailors on USS Arizona deck, 84-26-33, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Navy Admiral Olmsted Inspecting Torpedo Division on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-34, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Vought 03U Corsair Plane Leaving Catapult, 84-26-35, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Vought 03U Corsair Plane Above Water with Catapult in Foreground, 84-26-36, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - USS Los Angeles, CA-135, at Shanghai, China, 84-26-37, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Bull Fight in Panama, 84-26-38, circa 1925 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - New York, NY Skyline at Night, 84-26-39, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Elevated Railroad at 34th and Broadway, New York, NY, 84-26-40, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Governor's Island, New York Bay, 84-26-41, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified Battleships at Sea, 84-26-42, circa 1923 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified Battleships at Sea, 84-26-43, circa 1923 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Unidentified Battleships at Sea, 84-26-44, circa 1923 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Captain Ward K. Wortman on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-45, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - USS Arizona 1927-1928 4th Division Posing with Alligators at Guantanamo Bay, Cuba (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Plane Leaving Catapult on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-47, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Sailor Red Norman Sitting on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-48, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Sailor Bear on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-49, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Sailor Jack Dillon Standing on a Beach, 84-26-50, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Grounded Ships at Honda Point, CA, 84-26-51, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Grounded Ships at Honda Point, CA, 84-26-52, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - USS Chauncy Grounded at Honda Point, CA, 84-56-53, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Grounded Ships at Honda Point, CA, 84-26-54, circa 1929 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Sailor Holding Pelican, Ship's Channel, San Pedro, CA, 84-26-55, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified Sailor Holding Pelican, Ship's Channel, San Pedro, CA, 84-26-56, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Sailors holding Pelican, San Pedro, CA, 84-26-57, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Sailors holding Pelican, San Pedro, CA, 84-26-58, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - USS Arizona Glempic Cup Boat Race, 1st Place Cup, 84-26-59, 1924 September 18 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Two Unidentified Members of the USS Arizona Boat Crew Posing with Olympic Cup, 84-26-60, 1924 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Sailors Hostensky, Gleason and Unidentified Sailor in USS Arizona Football Uniform, 84-26-61, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Racing Cutter on Lake Union, Seattle, WA, 84-26-62, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Race Boat Crew Training on Kitsap Lake, Bremerton, WA, 84-26-63, 1925 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - USS Arizona Baseball Team, 84-26-64, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Unidentified Woman in Pearls, 84-26-65, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Unidentified Woman in Hat, 84-26-66, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Unidentified Sailor with Two Unidentified Women, 84-26-67, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified Woman Posing in front of Trees, 84-26-68, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Lorrain Martin Sitting on Porch, 84-26-69, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Two Unidentified Women Sitting on a Bench, 84-26-70, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Unidentified Women Sitting on Wooden Fence, 84-26-71, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - USS California and USS New Mexico at Sea, 84-26-72, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified Ships in Costa Rica, 84-26-73, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 84-26-74, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - USS Arizona Conning Tower, 84-26-75, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Frontal View of USS Arizona at Sea, 84-26-76, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - USS Pennsylvania and USS California with Unidentified Battleships in Formation in San Francisco, CA Bay, 84-26-77, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Gun on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-78, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - V Boat Observation Plane in San Francisco, CA Bay, 84-26-79, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Queen's Palace YMCA, Honolulu, HI, 84-26-80, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Depressurization Tank, New London, CT, 84-26-81, circa 1925 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Five Unidentified sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-82, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-83, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Three Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-84, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified Sailor on USS Arizona deck, 84-26-85, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Chief Petty Officer, 84-26-86, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Boxing in Wooden Ring, 84-26-87, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Sitting in Woods, 84-26-88, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors camping, 84-26-89, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Sailors Posing after Baseball Game, 84-26-90, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Group of Sailors Posing with Crocodiles in Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 84-26-91, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - USS Arizona Seamen Guard with Two Women, Seattle, WA, 84-26-92, 1929 August 09 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-93, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Sailors Garold and Joe Potenzias on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-94, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - All Navy Rifle Team, 84-26-95, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Sailor Dick Force Standing in a Park, 84-26-96, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified Sailors Drinking in a Small Docked Boat, 84-26-97, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified Sailors Drinking in a Small Docked Boat, 84-26-98, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified Sailor with Tige and At Em', Ship Dogs, San Pedro, CA, 84-26-99, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - USS Arizona Electrical Division Crew, 84-26-100, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing on Steps of Unidentified Building, 84-26-101, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Unidentified Destroyers with Smoke Screen, 84-26-102, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Unidentified Commander / Executive Officer of USS Arizona, 84-26-103, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Sailors on USS Arizona Conning Tower, 84-26-104, circa 1918 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - At Em' Arizona Boat at Sea, 84-26-105, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - USS Arizona Diving Party Boat at Sea, 84-26-106, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Sailor Red Lewis, 1st Class Machinists' Mate, 84-26-108, circa 1930 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - San Pedro, CA Lighthouse, 84-26-109, circa 1928 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Martin Kos and Albert Kos on Porch at Chicago Home on Leave, 84-40-2, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Picture Postcard Portrait of Martin Kos Taken for Parade in Brooklyn, Memorial Day, 84-40-3, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Martin Kos at Home on Leave, 84-40-4, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - USS Arizona Exploding Next to USS Nevada, Peral Harbor, HI, 84-27-3, 1941 December 7 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - USS Arizona Exploding Next to USS Nevada, Peral Harbor, HI, 84-27-4, 1941 December 7 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - USS Arizona Band at Block Arena the Night of December 6, 1941, 84-29-1 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - United States Marine Corp USS Arizona Row Team, 85-3-1, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - USS Arizona Landing Force Training Crew, 85-4-1, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Sailor John Stutz and Unidentified Sailor on Dock, 85-4-2, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Sailor John Stutz Posing Next to Tree, 85-4-3, circa 1935 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Landing Force Practice, 85-4-4, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - USS Arizona 5" 51 Caliber Broadside Gun, 85-4-5, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona 5" Anti-Aircraft Gun, 85-4-6, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - USS Arizona Motor Launch Nests, 85-4-7, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - 14" Shells on USS Arizona Deck, 85-4-8, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - 5" Guns on Pier on Bremerton, WA Dry Dock, 85-4-9, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Bulge in USS Arizona Hull, Bremerton, WA Dry Dock, 85-4-10, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - USS Arizona Rudder in Bremerton, WA Dry Dock, 85-4-11, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Sailors Patrick and Young, 85-8-1, circa 1937 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Neptune's Court Ceremony Victim on Operating Table, 85-8-2, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Neptune's Court Ceremony Victim in Stocks, 85-8-3, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Three Pollywogs in Stocks during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-4, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Electric Chair Used during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-5, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Electric Chair and Equipment Used during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-6, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Officer in Shorts and Peg Leg Pete during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-7, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Sailors Kline and Callahan, 1st Division Pollywogs during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-8, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Chairs for Dumping Pollywogs into Pool during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-9, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Unidentified Pollywog being dumped into Plunge during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-10, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified Pollywog being dumped into Plunge during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-11, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Unidentified Pollywog Going Down Chute during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-12, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Unidentified Pollywog Going Down Chute from Plunge Running Gauntlet of Canvas Club during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-13, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Shellbacks on Deck of USS Arizona during Neptune's Court Ceremony, 85-8-14, 1940 July 24 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - View of USS Arizona Stern, 63-32-2, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - 31 sheets of 35 mm copy negatives, various accession numbers, undated (Box 26 A, Folder 1)
    - 31 sheets of 35 mm copy prints, various accession numbers, undated (Box 26 A, Folder 2)
    - 29 sheets of copy prints, various sizes, various accession numbers, undated (Box 26 A, Folder 3)
    - 25 35mm Slides, USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, undated (Box 26 B)
  - Subseries 3: 8x10 Photographs, circa 1920-1976
    This subseries contains 8x10 black and white photographs and is arranged numerically by accession number. Materials are described at the item level. Materials document the ship at various locales, interior and exterior views of the ship, and various onboard weaponry and arsenal. This subseries also contains materials that document crew engaging in daily duties and personal activities, the ship at the Panama Canal in 1931, and the USS Arizona Memorial at Pearl Harbor, Hawaii. A portion of the materials document the December 7, 1941 Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor, Hawaii and the bombing of the USS Arizona in particular. Certain materials are duplicated in other series within the collection. Item titles contain a three digit accession number assigned by the University of Arizona Student Union upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction.
    - Dedication Ceremonies for Plaque for USS Arizona, 50-1-1, 1950 December 7 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Plaque Unveiled at Hulk of Sunken USS Utah, Pearl Harbor, HI, Official Navy Photograph, 50-1-2, 1950 December 7 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - USS Arizona Shipmates at Reunion, Bremerton, WA, 62-1-1, 1937 May 15 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Stern View, 63-3-1, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona and USS Nevada in Formation, 67-4-1, circa 1932-1935 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Gun Barrel from a Forward Turret of the USS Arizona Being Greased with Cosmoline by Unidentified Sailors, 67-4-2, circa 1932-1935 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - United States Flag at USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 68-5-1, Color Print, 1968 November (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Group of People at USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 68-5-2, Color Print, 1968 November (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona at the Brooklyn Bridge, Departing New York as Part of Escort for President Wilson on His Way to Paris Peace Conference, 71-4-1, From the Archives of Carlos Wilfred Cecil, 1918 December 13 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Photograph Taken from Japanese Plane during Initial Attack at Pearl Harbor, 73-2-1, 1941 December 7 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Japanese Representatives on board the USS Missouri during Japanese Formal Surrender, 73-2-2, 1945 September 2 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - General MacArthur Signing Japanese Formal Surrender on board USS Missouri, 73-2-3, 1945 September 7 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - USS Lexington in Culebra Cut, Panama Canal, Color Tint Print, 77-3-5, circa 1925 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Scuba Diver in Water, 77-3-282, 1940 May 22 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - USS Arizona Roster of Officers, 77-4-1, Copy Photograph, 1941 June 1 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Wreckage of USS Arizona Bow, 77-4-2, 1942 May 18 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - General Cleaning Operations after Port Leg of Foremast Removed from USS Arizona Wreckage, 77-4-3, 1942 May 18 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Removing Projectiles from Turret #4 from USS Arizona Wreckage, Fantale Crane in Background, 77-4-4, 1942 May 18 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Arizona II Christening Ceremony, Honolulu, HI, 77-5-1, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Mrs. Hogan Christening Arizona II, Honolulu, HI, 77-5-2, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. Hogan Christening Arizona II, Honolulu, HI, 77-5-2, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - President Hoover and Captain Freeman Seated on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-1, Copy, 1931 March (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - President Hoover and Captain Freeman Seated on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-1, Copy, 1931 March (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - President Hoover and Captain Freeman Seated on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-1, Copy, 1931 March (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - President Hoover and Captain Freeman Seated on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-1, Copy, 1931 March (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - President Herbert Hoover and Secretary of Navy Patrick Hurley on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-2, 1931 March (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - President Herbert Hoover and Secretary of Navy Patrick Hurley on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-2, 1931 March (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - President Herbert Hoover and Secretary of Navy Patrick Hurley on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-2, 1931 March (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - President Herbert Hoover and Secretary of Navy Patrick Hurley on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-2, 1931 March (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 84-26-3, circa 1920 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, Copy, 84-26-3, circa 1920 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, Copy, 84-26-3, circa 1920 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 84-26-4, circa 1920 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, Copy, 84-26-4, circa 1920 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal Locks, 84-26-5, circa 1925 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal Locks, 84-26-5, Copy, circa 1925 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - USS Arizona at Sea with Sailors on Deck, 84-26-6, circa 1925 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - USS Arizona at Sea with Sailors on Deck, 84-26-6, Copy, circa 1925 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 84-26-7, circa 1925 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Captain Isaac C. Kidd, USN, USS Argonne, 84-26-8, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Painting of Captain Isaac C. Kidd, Painted Posthumously by Rishell, 84-26-9, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal after Refitting on Way to Join Pacific Fleet, 84-26-112, Contains Copy, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - USS Nevada Being Run Aground at Hospital Point to Avoid Being Sunk by Japanese Submarine during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-5, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Ford Island Hangers being bombed during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-6, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 3 USS Cassin, USS Downes, USS Pennsylvania Destroyed in Dock After Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-7, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Sailors Abandoning USS California during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-8, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Captured Japanese Photograph of Japanese Carrier Plane Taking off for Pearl Harbor, 84-27-9, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Looking Toward Shipyard from Bravo Pier during Pearl Harbor Attack, Cruiser Helena is on left, Capsized Minelayer Ogala on right, Smoke Rising from Destroyer Shaw in the Background, BB Nevada Underway at center right, 84-27-10, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Captured Japanese Photograph of Aerial View of Attack on Pearl Harbor, 84-27-11, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - USS Arizona Wreckage in Pearl Harbor, 84-27-12, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona Forward Mast falling in Plume of Smoke during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-13, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - USS Arizona Forward Mast falling in Plume of Smoke during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-13, Copy, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - USS Arizona Forward Mast falling in Plume of Smoke during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-13, Copy, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Attack on Naval Air Station during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-17, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - View from Ford Island Looking Toward Shipyard with SS Narwhale in Foreground during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-24-15, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Damage to USS Cassin and USS Downed in Drydock #1 with USS Pennsylvania in Background during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-16, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Representative C.W. Nimitz Signing Japanese Surrender on USS Missouri, 84-27-17, 1945 September 2 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified Ship on Fire during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-19, 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-1, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified Marine Standing Guard at USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-2, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Two Unidentified Marines Standing Guard at USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-2, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - USS Arizona Memorial Site before Construction, 84-28-5, circa 1962 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - USS Arizona Memorial Site before Construction, 84-28-5, Copy, circa 1962 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - USS Arizona Memorial Site before Construction, 84-28-5, Copy, circa 1962 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - View Showing the United States Flag Flying above the USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-6, 1962 July (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Cpl. Thomas J. Darby, United States Marine Corp, Standing Honor Guard Duty Aboard the USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-7, 1962 July (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-8, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Wall of Names of those who perished on the USS Arizona during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-28-9, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Two Unidentified Marines Standing Guard at Wall of Names of those who perished on the USS Arizona during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-28-10, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Sign Listing the Number of Arizonans that Enlisted in United States Navy in a Particular Year, 84-28-11, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Wall of Names of those who perished on the USS Arizona during Pearl Harbor Attack with Wreath, 84-28-13, color print, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Wall of Names of those who perished on the USS Arizona during Pearl Harbor Attack with Wreath, 84-28-13, color print, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI from Water, 84-28-14, color print, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Foundation for no. 3 Gun Turret at USS Arizona Memorial Site, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-15, color print, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - USS Oklahoma City at Partially Competed USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-2, 1962 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Opening of USS Arizona Memorial, 84-29-3, 1963 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Aerial View of Pearl Harbor and Naval Air Station after Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-29-4, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-5, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Memorial with City in Background, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-6, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Aerial View of Naval Air Station Air Strip, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-7, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Memorial with Naval Air Station in Background, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-8, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Memorial with Naval Air Station in Background, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-9, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Memorial with Naval Air Station on left and Land in Background, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-9, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Memorial with Naval Air Station on Right, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-9, contains copy, circa 1963 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Aerial View of Battleships Destroyed during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-29-12, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Row of Battleships at Sea, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-29-13, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Aerial View of Ford Island Naval Air Station, 84-29-14, circa 1945 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 84-29-15, contains copy, circa 1941 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Unidentified Ships Sunken during Pearl Harbor Attacks, 84-29-16, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 28, Folder 46)